wikifoundry.com 2016-04-17

# Privacy - WikiFoundry

Last Revised: December 3, 2010

This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by WikiFoundry.com, Inc. (“WikiFoundry”, “we” or “us”) with respect to your use of the Web sites located at [http://www.wetpaint.com](http://www.wetpaint.com/), [http://www.wikifoundrycentral.com](http://www.wikifoundrycentral.com/) and any Wikis by WikiFoundry Web sites hosted through the service (the "Sites"), so you can make an informed decision about using the Sites. **We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the Policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.**   

## What is Personal Information?

As used herein, the term "personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number, e-mail address, or credit card number), or information about that individual that is directly linked to personally identifiable information. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Sites or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.   

## Personal Information We Collect

Active Collection: We collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us when you visit the Sites. For example, depending on the specific web site, you may provide us with personal information when you register as a member and set up an account, sign up to receive our daily news feed, subscribe to an email notification or contact us by email. Such information may include personal information, such as your name and email address. Personal and demographic information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with posting any comments or materials on or through the site or participating in any other interactive forums or features on the Sites. In addition, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you provide in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities on the Sites. 

Passive Collection: When you use the Sites, some information is also automatically collected, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and your activity on the Sites. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only. 

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" or web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive at the request of a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Sites and your experience. If we link cookies to any personally identifying information, we will treat this information as personal information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser manufacturer to learn about these functions. However, if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or Services on our Sites. Web beacons are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on the Sites or in emails relating to the Sites to collect certain information and monitor user activity on the Sites. 

We may also use third parties to serve ads on the Sites or to provide analytic services. These third parties may place cookies, web beacons or other devices on our Sites and your computer to collect non-personal information, and information provided by these devices may be used, among other things, to analyze data, to determine the popularity of certain content, to determine what ad content to provide, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests, to track the interests or users and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Sites and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or web beacons placed by third parties., and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

We may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. 

## How We Use Personal Information

We use personal information collected through our Sites for the purposes described in this Policy or elsewhere on the Sites. For example, we may use personal information we collect: 

  * to operate the Sites, to provide the services, products, or information you request, and to process and complete any transactions in connection therewith; 
  * to request feedback and to otherwise contact you about your use of the Sites; 
  * to respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests, and complaints and provide customer service; 
  * to monitor and analyze site usage and trends, and to customize, personalize and improve the Sites and our users' experiences on the Sites, such as providing ads, content, or features that match their profiles or interests, and to increase the Sites' functionality and user friendliness; 
  * to provide you with news and information about our or third party events, activities, offers, promotions, products, and services we think will be of interest to you; 
  * to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Sites; 
  * to notify you about important changes to our Sites; 
  * to notify and contact contest and sweepstakes entrants; and 
  * for any other purpose for which the information was collected.

We may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. 

## What Personal Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

We will not share the personal information we collect from you through the Sites with third parties, except as described in this Policy or on the Sites. For example, we may share personal information as follows: 

  * with vendors, consultants, and other service providers ("Service Providers") who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Sites or the services we provide and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us; 
  * in an aggregated or anonymized form that does not directly identify you; 
  * when you give us your consent to do so, such as if you opt in to receive marketing communications from third parties on our news feed subscription page or if we otherwise notify you on the Sites that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information; 
  * when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to: (a) comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants, or court orders; or (b) protect the rights, property, or safety of WikiFoundry, our users, our employees, copyright owners, third parties or the public, including without limitation to protect or WikiFoundry our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate, or unlawful use of our Sites; 
  * to enforce or apply this Policy, our Terms of Use, or our other policies or agreements; and 
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where personal information may be disclosed or transferred as one of the business assets of WikiFoundry. 

The Sites may include features which enable you to post comments, content or otherwise share information through Facebook or other third party social media sites. You understand that if you use such features or otherwise post any comments, content or other information to or through the Sites, the information you post will be available to other users and other web sites and in some cases may be publicly available. We recommend you be cautious about giving out personal information to others or sharing personal information through the Sites. 

We are not responsible for the actions of Service Providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to any third parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices before disclosing information directly to any such parties. Nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregated or anonymized information, which may be shared with third parties without your consent. 

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our Sites may contain links to other websites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. This Policy does not apply to such linked sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites or any other sites that are linked to from the Sites. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.   

## What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information Online?

We have put into place reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission that can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.   

## What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Use of Your Information?

You may "opt out" of receiving marketing or promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations.   

## Questions?

If you have any questions about this Policy, please [contact us](http://www.wetpaint.com/contact-us). (http://www.wetpaint.com/contact-us)
